{
    "subject": "resource/Inseminoid",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:British_science_fiction_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of the film Inseminoid is British science fiction films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9634749293327332,
            "question": "Is Inseminoid considered a science fiction film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8662027716636658,
            "question": "How is Inseminoid similar to other British science fiction films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6807127594947815,
            "question": "What genre is the film Inseminoid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6436737775802612,
            "question": "What are some common themes in British science fiction films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6104387640953064,
            "question": "What makes Inseminoid a notable film within the genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6088253855705261,
            "question": "Can you give me an example of a British science fiction film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5662909150123596,
            "question": "What is the nationality of films like Inseminoid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5111525654792786,
            "question": "Are there any other famous British science fiction films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.497243732213974,
            "question": "Where does the film Inseminoid originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4957667887210846,
            "question": "Are there any specific elements in Inseminoid that represent its British origin?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of the film Inseminoid is British science fiction films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8997_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does the film Inseminoid originate from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8997_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other famous British science fiction films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8997_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of films like Inseminoid?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8997_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8997_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8997_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8997_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8997_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8997_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8997_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8997_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8997_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8997_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8997_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n\n\nLet me explain:\n\nSeveral documents clearly state that *Inseminoid* is a British science fiction horror film.  Therefore, the statement \"The subject of the film *Inseminoid* is British science fiction films\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while some of the documents mention that Inseminoid is a British independent feature film, and also mention it as a science fiction horror film directed by Norman J. Warren, there are no documents that categorically state that the subject of the film Inseminoid is \"British science fiction films\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to \"Inseminoid\" as a British science fiction horror film, which supports the statement that the subject of the film Inseminoid is indeed British science fiction films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n\nThe provided documents indicate that \"Inseminoid\" is indeed a British science fiction horror film, thus supporting the statement that its subject matter falls under the category of British science fiction films."
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The subject of the film Inseminoid is not exclusively British science fiction films. It falls under the subgenres of science-fiction horror, and while it was produced in the UK, it also incorporates elements from other genres and countries (such as the US with its alleged inspiration from Alien).",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the context information clearly states that Inseminoid is a British independent feature film of the science fiction genre, indicating that its subject is indeed British science fiction films.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}